The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
The Death energy here is really thick
and the killing intent
is at least 10 times fiercer than outside.
A newcomer !
He looks so clean and innocent.
He's got the kind of skin I love peeling the most !
Is this the scent of a newcomer ?
Perfect, time to kill another one
and drink his blood !
These are all felons awaiting their execution.
Fellow cultivator Wang, you can do as you please.
I wonder how many Life Seals
I can make with these prisoners.
5 days later
I felt an intense killing intent earlier.
Could it be...
that there is another secret
beneath this Hong Prison ?
The Celestial Slaughter Art
uses strands of killing intent
to refine Life Seals.
I have killed all of them
but only gained some useless Death energy.
What am I missing ?
Because you don't have enough urge to kill.
If you don't immerse yourself in slaughter
to refine a Killing Heart,
you will not be able to generate enough killing intent.
No matter how hard you try, it's useless.
Refine the heart through killing,
transform the heart into a demon.
That is my Demon Slaughter Dao.
If you wish to learn the true Demon Slaughter Dao,
I can grant you an opportunity.
But whether you can use it
will depend on your own fate.
What's the condition ?
As a warden,
I cannot leave the Hong Prison.
If you succeed,
I want you to use your slaughter spell
to kill the Demon General Shi Xiao !
Deal.
Follow me.
Such a powerful killing intent !
It's enough to stimulate my own killing intent.
It seems he wasn't lying.
This is where the Demon Emperor's sword is nourished.
Slaughter Blood Pool\NHong Prison
This place was created by the Emperor himself.
The killing intent here is so fierce
that it can invade your mind.
If your heart isn't strong,
I'm afraid you will end up like them
and turn into a walking corpse.
This is a one-way ticket,
have you thought it through ?
Nourish the Demon Emperor's sword ?
What a great place for slaughter !
This slaughter energy condensed from killing intent
should be perfect for cultivating the Celestial Slaughter Art.
Why am I unable to use it ?
Or is it...
that there isn't enough slaughter energy ?
Wrong...
3 days later
I'm still wrong !
What's the method to transform this slaughter energy
into strands of killing intent ?
Who's there !?
How could he be trapped here
with such a cultivation ?
Such fierce sword energy !
Is this silver dragon the Emperor's sword ?
Release me...
Let me out !
I see...
To leave this place
you must pass the Emperor's sword.
No wonder he said it was a one way ticket...
The Emperor's sword is strong,
I have no way of fighting it head-on.
If the slaughter energy is used to nourish the sword
and that same slaughter energy is born from prisoners killing each other,
then it stops if they all die.
Why would the Emperor's sword destroy its own food source ?
Could it be...
In this blood pool, no one is able to die.
The prisoners fight endlessly
to provide an endless supply of slaughter energy for the sword.
Who knows how many years these people have been trapped here.
If I want to get out,
I must master the Celestial Slaughter Art.
That's my only way out.
Now die !
You can't get out !
What am I missing ?
Transform Death into Life
and back into Death.
This perpetual cycle nourishes the Emperor's sword.
The Celestial Slaughter Art
is an imitation of a celestial spell.
It matches with your
Life and Death Domain.
That's why...
Use killing intent to take lives
and refine that life into a Life Seal !
Create Life with Death
and Death with Life !
Celestial Slaughter Art !
I'm finally free...
You...
You actually used the blood pool to your advantage !?
So the key to the Celestial Slaughter Art
was the Life and Death Reincarnation Cycle.
It's useless...
The Emperor's sword is coming...
You won't get out.
Killing intent...
Go !
It's over...
Even Demon Generals
are unable to block
the Emperor's sword.
From Life to Death...
Life Seals !
He actually withstood the Emperor's sword !?
Save me !
Farewell.
Sword Hall\NSky Demon City
Demon Emperor's sword
What kind of grievance has she suffered
to cause such anger ?
What is this ?
The Emperor's sword is angry.
A disaster is coming
and blood will flow.
How powerful
do you two think
Hai Zhu\NDa Lou Sword Sect disciple\NLate stage Soul Transformation
Wei Yang\NDa Lou Sword Sect disciple\NLate stage Soul Transformation
this sword is ?
Not inferior to Master's swords.
Mo Fei\NDemon General\NRank 250 000 Demonic Energy\N(Peak Late stage Soul Transformation)
That's the direction of...
the Hong Prison !?
The Emperor's sword
couldn't possibly be heading for Wang Lin, right ?
With Wang Lin's cultivation,
how could he offend the Emperor's sword ?
I must be overthinking...
Don't leave now if you want to stay alive.
Stay close to me.
We've stirred up a huge mess...
How did this guy manage to attract the Emperor's sword ?
If he gets caught,
I'll be implicated too...
Hurry, go !
And don't forget our deal.
Is there a place for secluded cultivation ?
Follow me.
Thank you.
So it really was him...
5 days later
My 3792 Life Seals
are complete.
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?